声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对：扣扣
后期：xyz 双语制作：ljw1911  七色九天
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
Emma!
我的妹妹  我的妹妹
My sister! My sister!
Emma! Emma!
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
-她没呼吸了  -我来看看
-She's not breathing.  -Watch out.
跟我来吧
Come with me.
别担心  她会没事的
Don't worry, she will be fine.
很好  把水吐出来  你还好吧?
Good. Let it out. You OK?
我的妈妈呢?
Where's my mom?
我不知道
I don't know
她在洛杉矶等我们
She's meeting us in Los Angeles .
Pam Pam  有人看到我妻子了么?  Pam
Pam! Pam! Anybody seen my wife?
我们还没到呢...
We're not there yet.
但是我向你保证我们马上会把你带回家的好么?
I promise, we’re gonna get you home soon, OK?
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你来照看一下孩子们好么?
Would you look after the children?
我还有点事
There is something I have to do.
好的
OK.
跟着这位好心的阿姨
Stay with this nice woman.
我马上回来
I'll be back in a minute.
我的腿  我的腿
My leg! My leg!
很严重么?  很严重  是么?
Is it bad? It's bad, isn't it?
还好  没那么严重
Nah, it's not that bad.
我在佛蒙特州滑雪的时候也弄伤了我的腿
I broke my leg skiing up at Stowe, in Vermont.
我当时滑得很快
I was on this run, going pretty fast.
在和那个英俊的巡警比赛
I was racing this cute ski patrol guy.
我追着他  失去了控制  然后...
I went off this mogul, lost my edge, and...
砰
Bam!
我的左腿骨折了
Snapped my left leg.
这很...
Now, that...
这很不好受
that was bad.
你是个医生?
You a doctor?
退学前我在医学院上过一年
Year of med school before I dropped out.
我是学临床心理学的
I'm a clinical psychologist.
你救了那个女孩,你是个医生?
You saved that girl's life. You a doctor?
不是
No.
救命
Help!
来帮帮忙
Hey! I need some help!
丛林里有人  他还活着
There's someone in the jungle! He’s alive!
救命  救救我  来人啊
Help! Help me! Please, help me!
救命
Help!
我们得爬上去
We should climb up...
-我抓稳他  你拉住他...  -不不  等等
-I'll hold him steady  you pull him  -No, no, wait.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
Bernard!
你会没事的  Bernard
You're gonna be all right, Bernard.
我要你解开你的安全带
I need you to unbuckle your seat belt
抓住你边上的树杈
and grab the branch next to you.
他死了么?  我想他死了
Is he dead? I think he's dead!
-也许我们得爬上去..  -不
-Maybe we should climb up.  -No.
你要集中注意力  Bernard
I need you to focus, Bernard.
解开安全带
Unbuckle your seat belt.
现在抓住你边上的树杈
Now, grab the branch next to you.
我想我做不到
I don't think I can do that.
Bernard  椅子快要掉下来了
Bernard, those seats are gonna fall.
加油  你能行的
Come on, you can do it.
Bernard!
好的
All right
抓紧点  好么?
hold on tight, OK?
我上来帮你
I'm coming up to get you.
有人有水么?
Does anybody have any water?
这儿没有
No. Not here.
找不到火柴?
Couldn't find any matches?
干的?
Dry ones?
你可以问问别人  但我没有
You can ask around, but I couldn't find any.
马上就要天黑了
It's gonna be dark soon.
我们得生火作信号  以便他们能找到我们
Gonna get a signal fire started so they can find us.
-你是做什么的  是童子军?  -是成年军
-What are you, a Boy Scout?  -Grown-up version.
我是美国和平队的
I'm in the Peace Corps.
他们还没解散么?
They still have that?
像你这种年纪的人还知道那是什么我深感欣慰
I'm just happy somebody your age actually knows what it is.
你叫什么?
What's your name?
Goodwin.
我叫Ana Lucia
I'm Ana Lucia.
我听说...
I heard
你是那个...
that you were
从海里把尸体拉上来的人
the one who pulled the dead bodies out of the water.
是的
Yes.
有看到一个黑人么?
Were any of them African-American?
没有
No.
是我的妻子...
It's my wife.
我找不到她
I can't find her.
我会为她祈祷的
I will pray for her.
见鬼的救援飞机怎么还不来?
Where the hell are the rescue planes?
我也会为他们祈祷的
I will pray for them, too.
怎么了?
What was that?
Libby
看好孩子
watch the kids.
在这儿
Over here.
好了  没事了
It's all right. We'll be OK.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
没找到皮夹
No wallets...
也没有手机
...no cell phone...
钥匙也没有  什么都没有
...no keys, nothing.
你还好吧?
Are you OK?
听着  有3个人失踪了...那个金发人
Look, three other people are missing. The blonde guy
还有那个卷发的  加上上次和我们一起救人的那个德国人
The curly haired guy, and the German who was helping us.
-你看见什么了么?  -没有
Did you see where they came from?  -No, I didn't.
他们有多少人?
How many there were?
我什么都没看到
No, I didn't see anything.
这些人是谁?
Who are these people?
我不知道  但是他们在丛林中  没穿鞋子
I don't know. But they're out here in the jungle with no shoes,
口袋里没有东西 衣服上也没有商标
nothing in their pockets, no labels on their clothes.
这些人是在我们之前来这个岛的
These people were here before us.
我们得离开海滩
We need to get off the beach.
我们得找个安全的地方
We need to find a safer place.
我们有孩子还有重伤者
We've got kids and people who are seriously hurt.
我们能到哪儿去?
Where are we gonna go?
我们怎么带上他们?
How are we gonna move them?
还有这烽火呢?
What about the signal fire?
我们都离开了海滩还怎么等救援呢?
How are we all gonna get rescued if we're off the beach?
Nathan说的对
Nathan's right.
他们有卫星  还有黑匝子
They have satellites. The black box.
我们不需要靠烽火来请求救援
We don't need a fire for them to find us.
不  我们需要
Yes, we do.
在坠机之前  飞行员说我们失去了联系  我们在往回飞
Before the crash, the pilot said we'd lost communication. We were turning back.
我们往另一个方向飞了有两小时之多
We were flying for two hours in the wrong direction.
他们不知道到哪儿来找我们
They don't know where to look.
他的腿...感染已经越来越严重了
His leg...the infection is getting worse.
他会是第四个死的人
He'll be the fourth to go.
我们还能怎么做?
What are we supposed to do about that?
加油  加油  抓住它抓住它
No, come here! Come on! Grab it! Grab it! Over here!
在这儿  来  在这儿
Come on! Over here!
我抓住了  抓住了  抓住了
I got it! I got it! I got it...
我抓住了  我抓住了 不!  好了  我已经抓住了  抓住了
I got it! I got it! Oh, no! I got it! All right...
要来些鸡肉么?
Would you like some chicken?
你有一周没说话了
You haven't said a word in a week.
你为什么不说话?
Why aren't you talking?
你知道  那不是你的错
It wasn't your fault, you know.
你只是在自我防卫
You were just defending yourself.
-这东西很管用  -是的
-That'll work.  -Yeah...
我在那儿听到了猪或是什么的叫声
I heard a pig or something out there.
也许我们明天能吃熏肉了
Maybe we can have some bacon tomorrow.
怎么了?
What?
你去哪儿了?
Where were you?
我去上厕所了
I had to go to the bathroom.
我们有规定
We have a system for that.
至少要两人一起去
We go in pairs.
抱歉
Yeah, sorry.
救命
Help us! Please!
孩子们
The kids!
他们抢走了孩子
They took the kids!
他们带走了Jed和Eli
I can't find them! And they took Jim and Eli!
Nancy不见了
Nancy's gone!
他们逃了
They're gone.
他们往哪儿去了?
Which way did they go?
醒醒  醒醒
Wake up! Wake up!
你是谁?  说话啊  醒醒
Who are you? Talk to me! Wake up!
她死了
She's dead!
She's dead.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
那是一把刀?
Is that a knife?
那是什么?
What is that?
是个名单
It's a list
什么名单?
A list of what?
我们之中的...九个人
Nine... of us.
没找到?
Nothing?
他们抢走了9个人
They drag nine people
包括孩子们
into the jungle, the kids...
而他们就没留一点痕迹?
...and there's no sign of them?
现在还不是一个说话的好时机么?
Now's not a good time to talk?
我们得想办法让你说话
What needs to happen to make you say something?
冷静点让我们仔细想想
Hey! Calm down, let's figure this out.
"冷静点"?
"Calm down,
"让我们仔细想想"?
let's figure this out"?
这是他们带走的九个人的名字...
Here are the names of every single person they took, all nine of them.
他们穿什么  他们长得怎样...全部都有
What they were wearing, what they look like.
他们中有人有我们的名册
One of them had a list of us.
他们可能是从已经带走的那些人的口里知道我们的名字的
They could a got our names from the people they took.
第一天晚上没人知道每个人的名字
Nobody knew any names the first night.
可能他们在监视我们
Maybe they're watching us.
你昨天消失了两个小时
You were gone for two hours yesterday.
什么?
What?
-你去哪儿了?  -我去上厕所了
-Where were you?  -I was going to the bathroom.
嘿  好了
Hey, stop!
我们都很害怕
We're all scared.
我们别在这儿瞎猜了
Let's not get paranoid here.
我们什么都不知道
We don't know anything.
他说的对
He's right.
他们为什么要在我们这儿卧底?
Why would they try to infiltrate us?
我是说  这很疯狂
Now, that's crazy.
不管他们是谁,他们知道我们在这儿
Well, whoever they are, they know we are here.
我们得离开海滩
We need to leave this beach.
你说我们得让烽火一直燃着
You said we needed to keep the signal fire burning.
我想我们该把它熄了
I think it's time we let it go out.
休息5分钟
Five minutes.
我们一路走了3天了
We've been walking for three days.
但是还只走到这儿  休息5分钟
And you're still here. Five minutes.
你知道么?  你们想继续走那就走吧
Know what? You all wanna keep walking, go ahead.
清水  有岩石作屏障 还有许多水果树
Fresh water, rock wall at our backs, lots of fruit trees,
这儿对我来说很不错
right here looks pretty good to me.
好吧
Fine. OK.
这地方不错
This'll work.
在海滩时  他们来的那个晚上
Back at the beach, the night they came back,
你说Nathan消失了两个小时
you said that Nathan was gone for two hours, that he was missing.
我看到他是偷偷溜出去的  Ana
He creeps me out, Ana.
你真的认为我们中的一个人...
You really think it's possible that one of us is...
是他们的卧底么?
one of them?
那你想我挖这个洞来做什么?
Why do you think I'm digging this hole?
这东西真能抓住野兔么?
We gonna catch rabbits with this?
是的  再给我根棒子
Hell, yeah. Give me another stick.
嘿  Ana
Hey, Ana.
Ana!
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
你得和我谈谈  Nathan
You and I are gonna have a talk.
你马上放我出去
You let me out of here right now!
放我出去 放我出去  否则...
You let me out! You let me out, or I'll...
我什么都没做  Ana
I didn't do anything, Ana!
-他不是我们飞机上的  -什么?
-He wasn't on the plane.  -What?
我们飞了两个多小时
We were in the air two hours.
我没见过他  一次都没有
I didn't see him once. Not once.
飞机很大  Ana 只是因为你没有...
It's a big plane.
不  我也没看到过他
I didn't see him either.
我很善于记住乘客的样子 而且我肯定没见过他
I'm pretty good with faces, of the passengers. I did not see him.
等等  你们在开玩笑吧
You're not all serious
他从没说起过他自己...Nathan
He never talks about himself. Nathan.
每次我问他什么的时候  他总是回避
Every time I ask him anything, he just dodges.
不  如果他是他们中的一个  那为什么他还在这儿?
If he were one of them, why would he still be here?
我不知道  但我要找出答案
I don't know, but I'm gonna find out.
让我出去好么?  Ana
Will you let me out? Ana?
你有意见么?
You got a problem with this?
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything.
让我出去
Let me out!
孩子们在哪儿?
Where are the kids?
你从哪儿来  Nathan?
Where you from, Nathan?
加拿大
Canada.
你在澳大利亚干什么?
What were you doing in Australia?
我们整个驻军连返回美国
Company retreat.
-他们在哪儿?  -什么?
-Where are they?  -What?
你们连的其他弟兄  他们在哪儿?
The rest of your retreat. Where are they ?
他们不在飞机上
They weren't on the plane.
我自己多留了几天四处逛逛
I stayed extra days to sightsee.
为什么在飞机上没人见过你  Nathan?
How come nobody saw you on the plane?
-我在厕所里  -两小时?
-I was in the lavatory.  -For two hours?
我不记得在飞机上见过你
I don't remember seeing you.
那是因为你不在飞机上
That's because you weren't on it.
孩子们在哪儿  Nathan?
Where are the kids, Nathan?
孩子们在哪儿?
Where are the kids?
不再和我说话了么?
You're not talking to me anymore?
你后面的是什么?
What's that behind you?
站起来
Get up.
我说了  "站起来"
I said, get up!
-是谁给他吃的?  -怎么了?
-Who gave him food?  -What?
我想知道他对我们做了什么  你是负责看守他的
I'm trying to find out what they did, and you're taking care of him.
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything.
如果是你错了呢  Ana?
And what if you're wrong, Ana?
我们甚至不知道是否真的有卧底
We don't even know that there is spy.
是谁说的让我们呆在海滩上好让他们一个个把我们带走的?
Whose idea was it to stay at the beach where they could pick us off one by one?
他说的  Nathan
His. Nathan's.
自从你把他囚在那儿后 他们再也没来过
Well, they haven't come since we put him in there.
是谁干的?
Who did it?
是你?
You?
我们很为你担心  Ana
I'm worried about you, Ana.
你关了他4天了
You've had him down there four days.
我向那个小女孩保证过我会把她带回她母亲身边的
I promised that little girl that I would get her back home to her mom.
你有孩子么  Ana?
Do you have any kids, Ana?
没有
No.
我们得放了他
We should let him go.
我们不是野蛮人
We're not savages.
如果我是个野蛮人我早砍下他的手指了
If I were a savage I would have cut off his finger already.
明天我就打算这么干
That's tomorrow.
抓住绳子  我拉你上来
Grab the rope. I'll pull you up.
Ana Lucia  我想...
Ana Lucia's... I think...
我想我们都认为她会伤害你
We all think she's gonna hurt you.
现在你得离开这儿
You need to get away from here.
这儿有些水果  好了  马上走
There's some fruit in there, now just go.
海滩是哪个方向?
Which way's the beach?
往那儿走  大约5英里
That way, maybe five miles.
早上好
Morning.
Ana Lucia!
-他逃了  -什么?
-He's gone!  -What?
他逃了  Nathan逃走了
He's gone! Nathan's gone!
Ana  你打算怎么办?
Ana, what are you gonna do?
他们找到我们了  是时候离开了
They found us, it's time to move.
那是什么?
What is it?
我不知道  像是一个碉堡
I don't know. Some sort of bunker.
你想这是他们的么?
Do you think it's theirs?
你干什么?
What are you doing?
这是什么地方?
What is this place?
像是储藏室什么的
Looks like some sort of storage facility.
嘿  来这儿看看
Hey, come over here.
那是什么?  拿去
What was that? Get it.
这儿还有什么?
What else is in here?
是玻璃假眼
It's a glass eye.
看看这个
Look at this.
是无线电
It's a radio.
喂?
Hello?
喂?  有人么?
Hello? Can anybody hear me?
电波被山挡住了
The hills are blocking it.
要信号的话  我们得去高一点的地方
If we want a signal, we need to get to higher ground.
我去吧
I'll do it.
我和你一起去
I'll go with you.
不  你得呆在这儿  把这儿打点成一个庇护所
No, you stay here. Get this place set up as a shelter.
我们会的
We can all set it up.
我们几小时后就能回来  走吧
We can make it back in a couple of hours. Let's go.
你想他们为什么这么做?
Why do you think they're doing this?
什么他们为什么这么做?
Why do I think who's doing what?
他们
Them.
你就没想过他们为什么要攻击我们么?
Don't you ever wonder why they attack us?
也许他们不是在攻击我们
Maybe they're not attacking us.
是啊  他们只是不时的把我们往丛林里拖
Yeah, they just drag us into the jungle every now and then.
没有伤害我们
No real harm done.
说得好
Good point.
你想他们为什么只带走了我们中的一些人而不是另一些人?
Why do you think they take some of us and not the others?
你知道  第一晚  他们带走了我们中最强壮的
That first night they took the strongest of us,
你那沉默的朋友 还有另外3个人
our quiet friend, three other guys.
他们都是运动能手
They're all athletic...
强壮...
tough...
有威胁
threats.
但他们没带走你
They didn't take you.
我想在死了两个人后他们改变主意了
Guess they changed their plan after two of them got killed.
要休息一下么?
Wanna take a break?
好主意
Yeah, that's a good idea.
借刀用一下好么?
Can I have the knife?
谢谢
Thank you.
你想他们这把刀是怎么来的?
Where do you think they got it?
我是说  他们甚至连鞋子都没有
I mean, they don't even wear shoes.
他们怎么会有军刀的?
How did they get an army knife?
什么?
Sorry?
那把刀  是美军的军刀
The knife. It's US military.
拿来
Here...
我指给你看
I'll show you.
看到这个标志了么?
You see the tang stamp?
这把刀可能有20年的历史了
This knife's probably 20 years old.
现在是见不到了
You don't see these anymore.
但在这个岛上却有一把
Yet, here it is, on this island.
很奇怪  不是么?
Weird, huh?
我能问你点问题么?
Can I ask you something?
当然  Ana
Sure, Ana.
坠机那天你从丛林里跑出来
When you ran out of the jungle, the day of the crash...
你是怎么...你是怎么发现树上的Bernard的?
...how did you find Bernard up in the tree?
我在海滩上听见他喊救命了
I heard him shouting from the beach.
在海滩上?
From the beach?
你为什么这么问  Ana?
Why are you asking me about that, Ana?
他在那儿看到你了么?
Did he see you out there?
这就是为什么你要假装你是我们中的一员?
Is that why you pretended to be one of us?
你在坠机后10分钟从丛林里跑出来全身都是干的
You ran out of the jungle ten minutes after the crash. You weren't wet.
你不是从水里上来的
You were never even in the ocean.
他们在哪儿?
Where are they?
你的朋友
Your friends?
Nathan  你为什么...
Nathan... what did you...
即使你砍了他的手指  他还是会说他是飞机上的
If you had cut off his finger and he still told you he was on the plane,
我想你也许会认为弄错人了
I think maybe you would have started to believe you had the wrong guy.
你杀了他?
Did you kill him?
Nathan不是个好人
Nathan was not a good person.
这就是为什么他的名字不在名单上
That's why he wasn't on the list.
孩子们呢?你也杀了他们?
What about the kids? Did you kill them, too?
孩子们很好
The children are fine.
他们现在境况很好
They're better off now.
Goodwin呢?
Where's Goodwin?
现在这儿安全了
We're safe here now.
你为什么还在那东西上浪费时间? 这儿没信号
Why are you wasting time with that thing? There's no signal.
我一天只开一会
I only turn it on a couple minutes a day.
-这真的很不...  -喂
-It really doesn't...  -Hello?
喂?  那儿有人么?  求救求救
Hello? Anybody out there? Mayday! Mayday!
-有人么?  -喂?  喂?
-Is there someone there?  -Hello! Hello!
-那是谁?  -能听见我说话么?
-Who is that?  -Can you hear me?
请你再说一遍
Repeat your transmission.
喂  我们是大洋航空815航班的幸存者 请回答
Hello! We're survivors of the crash of Oceanic flight 815, please copy!
我们是815航班的幸存者
We're the survivors of flight 815!
不  等等  你干什么?
No, wait a minute, what are you doing?
是他们
It's them.
他们想引蛇出洞  他们想找到我们
They're trying to draw us out. They’re trying to find us.
不  他说了"815" 他说了"815航班"
No, he said "flight 815".
他们知道我们的航班号是因为Goodwin也知道
They know our flight number because Goodwin knew our flight number.
但是如果那儿真的有幸存者呢?
What if there are survivors out there?
没有幸存者了
There are no survivors.
现在是我们的生活了
This is our life now.
要学着适应适应了
Get used to it.
你看什么?
What are you looking at?
会没事的
It's going to be OK.
什么  你现在说话了?
What, you're talking now?
已经40天了
It's been 40 days.
你等了40天才说话?
You been waiting 40 days to talk?
你等了40天才哭
You waited 40 days to cry.
Libby.
把他翻过来
Turn him over.
他还活着么?
Is he alive?
去叫Ana Lucia  快
Get Ana Lucia! Quick!
你是谁?
Who are you?
你从哪儿来?
Where are you from?
-他不懂英语  -这不代表什么
-He doesn't speak English.  -That doesn't mean anything.
我们是在水里找到他的
We found him in the water.
他手腕上有个破手铐
He has a broken handcuff on his wrist.
我不确定他是否是个危险人物
I'm not sure that he's a threat.
他跑了
He's running!
Michael! Sawyer!  -Jin!
来人啊 来人啊   来人啊   来人啊  来人啊
Others! Others! Others! Others! Others...
来人啊
Others...
-打我  -打你?
-Hit me.  -Hit you?
你觉得他们没问题?
You think they're OK?
我们去找答案吧
Let's find out.
打我吧
Hit me.
-Cindy  Cindy在哪儿?  -被他们带走了?
-Cindy? Where's Cindy?  -Did they take her?
Cindy
Cindy!
是谁?
What was that?
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====